

CONTACT ME AT

- Home Address: Leurshoek 61 9120 Beveren, Belgium
- aaronfrans@hotmail.com
- +32 476 08 65 38

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• C#
- ••• C++
- •••• Unity
- ••• Software Development
- ••• Database Management
- • • Website Develpoment
- • • Communication
- •••• Work Ethic

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- •••• English
- •••• Dutch

SPECIAL DIPLOMAS

Finished the Oracle Database course. (2020)

AARON FRANS

JUNIOR GAME DEV

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a passionate Belgian developer who has explored various facets of game development. Without a doubt, it is the domain of AI that truly interests me. Among the many aspects of AI development, I find particular joy in crafting behaviors and pathfinding algorithms. These areas allow me to delve deeper into the intricacies of creating intelligent systems that enhance the gaming experience. Another aspect of programming I enjoy is the development of various tools, both in engine and outside of it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship Junior Game Developer

Myron Games | Feb 2024 - July 2024

- Work in an existing code base to implement new features
- Work in team and check in for daily stand-ups
- Learn to debug and optimize a game in unity

Internship Full-Stack Developer for Websites

Innovatus BE | Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

- Make the Front- and backend of the angular jobs admin site
- Work in team and check in for weekly scrum meetings

Maintenance of school

Sint-Maarten Campus | Jul 2018 - Jun 2023

- During Summer holidays help clean the school
- Work in a team of 8 people to complete a large task

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Howest

Digital Arts & Entertainment | Okt 2021 - Jun 2024

- Learned to Program with C++.
- Learned to work with various engines
- Learned the videogame pipeline

Hogent

Degree in Programming | Okt 2019 - Jun 2021

- Learned full-stack development for android web and windows applications.
- Learned about programming ethics and time management.

Howest

Digital Arts & Entertainment | Okt 2018 - Jun 2019

- Learned to Program with C++.
- Learned to think critically about problems and how to solve them

Sint-Maarten Campus

Social & Technical Sciences | Sep 2012 - Jun 2018

- Learned about various sciences such as: Biology, Chemistry,
- Learned how to communicate with people.